Curriculum Vitae

Personal information

First name: Mika

Last name: Grootenboer

Address: Dordrecht, Netherlands

Phone number: -

Email: Grootenboer.mika@outlook.com

Birthdate: 19-12-1998, Dordrecht

Nationality: Netherlands

Gender: Man Driver license: B, AM

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mika-grootenboer-3b8b84145/

Personality: My name is Mika Grootenboer, I'm 20 years and currently a third-year

Computer Science student at the university of Rotterdam. I'm a hard worker

and I like to learn new information that will make me a better

Developer/Programmer.

Education

2016-present Bachelor Informatica, third year

Propaedeutic in Computer Science

Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences

2011-2016 HAVO Economy and Society

Stedelijk Dalton Lyceum Kapteynweg, Dordrecht

Work experience

2018-2019 intern Devops Redkiwi, Rotterdam

Together with a small team of four responsible for the servers and working

on the automation of updates.

2016-present Potatoes, vegetables and fruit (AGF) collaborator Jumbo, Dordrecht

Responsible for the AGF department, working together with a group of ten

colleagues.

Verantwoordelijk voor de AGF afdeling, samenwerken met een groep van 10

medewerkers.

2012-2016 Spotta folder deliverer, Dordrecht

Delivering flyers on Monday Tuesday in my neighborhood.

Other informatie

Languages: Netherlands Native language

English Good

Computer Knowledge: Basic knowledge van HTML, CSS, C#, F#, Python, SQL, Ansible, PHP, Kali,

Ubuntu, Windows

Project management: Basic knowledge Agile/ Scrum

Hobbies and Interest

Sporting, gaming and reading